Juhwan Lee

Cell: 360-593-6736 · ljh1230vvv@gmail.com · juhwan@pdx.edu · https://www.linkedin.com/in/juhwan-lee/

SUMMARY

Enthusiastic software engineer with extensive technical experience in software testing and full-stack web development in a professional team environment. Familiar with data structures, object-oriented programming, systems programming, algorithms, and relational databases. Successfully work in teams and self-directed settings with the ability to quickly learn and master new technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FASOO Software Engineer Intern Seoul, South Korea Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

- Worked as part of a four-member team under the Wrapsody Development team to accomplish an internship project called Wrapsody eCo Workspace
- Created a new tab called Workspace in Wrapsody eCo and linked a real-time open-source collaborative text editor called Etherpad to create a new collaboration space where users can freely share their opinions
- Presented Wrapsody eCo Workspace in front of the CEO, team leaders, and senior developers on the last day of the internship

MEDIAZEN
Software Engineer Intern

Seoul, South Korea Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

- Presented new application ideas for STT, TTS, NLU, and Computer Vision in front of the team leader and senior developers on the first week of the internship
- Created 1000 test scenarios for the advancement of ART (Automatic Recognition Test), a software testing automation tool
- Responsible for software testing of the Volkswagen Voice Control System and reporting test results in proper documentation form to the project manager

REPUBLIC OF KOREA NAVY

South Korea

Petty Officer Second Class, Administrative Clerk

Jan 2018 - Oct 2019

- Responsible for reporting the status of the FF-956's personnel to the fleet, flotilla, and squadron
- Assisted in administrative work in the secretary's office of the vice chief of naval operations

EDUCATION

PORTLAND STATE UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Portland, Oregon Jan 2020 - Mar 2023

- Overall GPA: 3.54 / 4.00
- Activities and Societies: Software Engineering Capstone Team Lead
- Academic Honors: President's List (Winter 2022), Dean's List (Spring 2022)
- Electives Taken: Natural Language Processing, Code Review, Web Development, Reinforcement Learning, Data Mining, Virtual Reality
- Software Engineering Capstone Project: Currently implementing a cross-platform fitness challenge app called Walktober that is integrated with built-in iOS and Android fitness tracking systems

PORTLAND STATE UNIVERSITY

Portland, Oregon Sep 2015 - Jun 2017

Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering

- Academic Honors: Received International Achievement Scholarships (\$12,000)
- Leave of Absence: Korean mandatory military service (Jun 2017 Jan 2020)

SKILLS

Technologies: C, C++, Python, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, HTML, CSS, SQL, Node.js, Linux, Vim, VScode, Git **Languages:** Native in Korean, Fluent in English